嫌な予感がする 何かを見落としている
After challenging Meruem to a
contest in order to buy time, Pouf was now scattering scales on the
citizens who were not yet hypnotized.
ハギャの部下達を一掃した カイト　ゴン　キルアが
This is my final chance!
そっちじゃ　ない。
Palm, take the four women still here with you.
結構な数だ…。
They didn't run away? No.
一定の距離を保ちつつ攻撃せよ
If they see me, it'll take too long to explain.
決して深追いはするな
That's true... I understand.
第２小隊は右から 第３小隊は　左から敵を挟み撃ち
Why did we put them on the truck, anyway?
俺もゴンも 全然　気づかなかった…
Let them know that we're looking to negotiate.
左右から来るぞ！
Once that's done, you're free.
気を抜くなよ！
It's probably a trap, right? That's what I'll tell the King.
チッ。
Wait... Just the fact that I'm doing the
enemy's bidding may anger the King.
あっ…。
I'm not gonna dig my own grave.
クッソ。
Fine, I'll try it.
木が邪魔だね。 ああ。
Can you drive?
森を抜けるしかないんじゃない？
Better than you.
罠だな。
It's important that he carries out his mission.
よし！　そのまま追い立てろ ハギャ様　予定通りに…
Perhaps I should keep an eye on him,
even if it means losing Pouf... Palm.
フフフ…　いいぞ　フラッタ。 うん？ おぉ…　フフ。 フン！
Welfin, once this is over, you're free.
射程圏内に獲物を追い込めれば
Go and see Gyro.
なんか違くないですか？ あぁ？
Don't get too cocky!
獲物を フラッタに追い込ませたり
I'll kill you!
草むらに隠れて待ち伏せしたり イケてないですよね。
Don't you dare speak his name! You would never understand!
百獣の王ですよね？ 王様なんだから隠れてないで ダっと獲物の前に出て
I understand, Zaikahal.
そのほうが全然イケてますって！
How...
あのなぁ…　これが百獣の王の 狩りの　やり方なんだよ。
How do you know
黙って見てろ！
my former...
はいはい　まぁ　私は
I didn't tell anyone.
レアものが食べれれば どうでもいいんですけどね。
I probably won't ever remember my former name, but we were buddies.
ザザン隊が 捕獲して運んで来た奴だ。
They're our enemies.
４の９３３　…と言われてもねぇ。
Enemies of NGL.
多分　女王様に献上してるな。 このところ　さらに食欲が 旺盛になって来てるんだ。
Am I wrong?
ありゃあ　すっげぇ王を産むぜ。 ねえな… とっくに女王様の腹の中だ。
Brovada has forgotten his past, but he was also one of us. Take him with you.
３日で動けるようになる奴なんて いるかよ。
How do you know?
そうとも言い切れんから レアものなんだ。
What do you mean?
奴らは普通の人間とは違う。
You told me to go see Gyro.
それは　お前が身を持って 思い知っているだろうが。
You'd only say that if you knew Gyro was alive.
今の俺だって　あの時とは違うぜ。
Yeah, that's true. But...
今度　あいつらに会った時は この手でゆっくり　なぶり殺して
I don't know that he's alive. I just can't believe otherwise.
ギッタギタに引き裂いて 食ってやるんだ。
Since we all "survived." He couldn't have just been digested.
なぜ　キメラアントが「念」を？ もう一度　調べ直してくれ。
Damn it... Damn it! Damn it!
何で　そいつに そんなに　こだわるんだよ。 聞きたいことがあってな。
Are you sure about this, Pouf?
お前には見えぬか？ こいつの体を覆う光が。
Ten minutes have passed, and I don't
see any sign of Pitou returning...
フフフフ… そうとも これは天より与えられた
Get out.
才能という運命　選ばれた者の力
Remove your bonds and use a truck to escape.
この能力を使いこなせば 俺が王になることすら可能！
Once you're outside, you'll understand
the current situation.
退避！　退避だ！
Killing Gyro wouldn't be enough to stop him.
あぁ…。 ん？
Stop!
あぁ…。
Youpi-dono... I have a message that must be
taken to the King immediately.
うぅ…！
Yes. And they're looking to exchange the woman for their allies that
have been taken hostage?
力量差を冷静に見極めて 矛を収めた判断力。
Right... We're having a contest, so I
don't need to tell the King.
恐らく　師団長クラス。
If Pouf was anticipating this, he's a smart one.
己の爪と牙… それが 世界の中心だと思っていた
You can go. Yes, sir. Once he's back, I need to tell Pouf.
それを少し振り回すと 他者の人生を 終わらせることができ
Still, what's Pitou doing right now?
これ以上の至福は　ないと…
Chimera Ants are the enemy.
だが　そうではなかった
Gyro's enemy...
上には上がいて 俺は頂点にいなかった
Our enemy!
死を代償に俺は思い知り しかし　強くなった
Youpi-dono!
今の俺達では　奴らを倒せない。
I am the Royal Guard Youpi. I've never been anyone else.
恐らく巣は近い。 奴らを追えば 女王に　たどり着ける。
If you attack me, I'll fight back. I have a few questions for you.
な…　何だ？
Don't get too cocky, you little punk!
才能が　どうとか…。
Something is missing...
短い…　そして愚かな夢だった
Marshal
フン！
Yes...
格が違う
that I have yet to defeat
決して覆ることのない あらかじめ決められた地位
a single time...
あっちで話そうよ。
That took much longer than expected.
は…　はい！
By now, Pitou must have returned...
俺の能力は 俺のためにあらず！
I hope the King hasn't grown impatient.
この方に…
Where's Youpi?
そして　この方が仕える王に
Where has Youpi gone?
奉仕するための力！
What's that?
あり得ない
Youpi?
まがまがしいオーラは！
I-It can't be...
ハッ！
There are still skilled enemies around!
ふん　にゃるほど。
I can now begin, yes?
何をお調べですか？
W-Wait, Meruem-sama!
君達の言う　レアものについて。
The situation has changed...
それは私も何度も調べましたが 本には書かれておらず…。
It's too dangerous! The contest is— The contest is off?
本じゃなくて 本人に聞いたほうが早いよね。
That means I have won.
君達も　そうするつもりで 彼を探してたんでしょ？
Tell me everything you know.
そ…　その通りではありますが…。 あった　あった。
Is that acceptable?
そうか　新しい記憶は
We're okay now?
脳の海馬と呼ばれる部位に 記録され
What do you mean, Palm?
古い記憶は大脳皮質に。
Killua deduced that she is special to the King.
それを引き出すには…。 ふん　にゃるほど。
But the Royal Guard is divided...
わっ！ あぁ　君　ちょっと来て。
Pitou tried to save and protect her, while Pouf tried to kill her.
「発」とは オーラを自在に操る技術。
In other words, she is a double-edged sword for the King. Wait, wait, wait, wait... I find that hard to believe.
念能力の集大成。
It's impossible for the Royal Guard to bicker
and defy the King's will!
それは　強化系 変化系
Is it? Then why are you and I here now?
具現化系
Wouldn't you say it's impossible for Soldier Ants
放出系　操作系
to side with humans? Adding humans to the gene pool
特質系という
has led to many events that would be
impossible for normal Chimera Ants.
６つの系統があり…。 あ…　あり…。
Can you be certain that I'm wrong?
んにゃ？
Sorry... My point is that
ふんふん。
their loyalty to the King.
オーラの量を増やし
There is a human that the
King cares deeply about.
オーラの流れを速やかにする。
"We must protect that human." "We must kill that human."
基礎修行は
Both reactions make sense.
この２つに大部分の時間を費やす。
For now, I'll concede that point to you.
念能力を使っての戦闘では
Why does that mean we're okay now? Twenty minutes have passed
since the initial wave of En.
この２つの優劣が…　が…。
But the King hasn't killed or captured us yet.
しょ…　勝敗を分ける
I don't get it...
大きな要因になるからだ。
What's going on here?
にゃるほど。
When the En was used, I was carrying this girl.
基本能力の他に
If the King had noticed, he would have come straight to me. He didn't because I had
concealed her within my hair.
能力者の個性が 色濃く反映される…
It's possible that he didn't realize
I was carrying another person.
個別能力というものがある。
Are you following me?
自分の志向と系統が 一致していれば…。
It seems logical, so I can't argue that... But I still don't see your point.
より強い能力発現の 確率が高まる。
If she's covered up, the King
can't find her with his En. Are you suggesting
ふんふん。
that we let Knuckle and Meleoron die,
rather than make an exchange?
それで　６つの系統の判別方法は？
Of course not... We'll offer to make an exchange.
水見式という方法が
But we'll try to buy as much time as we can. To accomplish that, we must hide her in a place
最も簡単で　一般的。
where the King cannot find her. Buy time? How long are we talking?
水見式？
Until the King dies.
あっ！ お！
Until the King dies? Sure, he has to die sometime...
水が増えて溢れ出したってことは 強化系だね。
But if we knew when he'd die,
we wouldn't have a problem!
強化系？
Why are we okay now?
念能力者ということですか？
Give me a proper explanation!
まぁね。 そうか！ 確か君は　レアものと 戦ったって言ってたよね？
The King will die, and it will happen soon.
そいつに殴られたことによって 精孔が開き オーラが目覚めたんだ。 精孔？
Within the next few hours, the King will die!
なるほど　コルトも ラモットの変化の原因は
We need to go deeper...
レアものとの戦いにあると 言っていましたが
Yes, we must put her in a place
where only we can find her.
うん　いいんじゃない？
That should do it.
それ　僕もやってみようかな。
All that's left is to negotiate, without going far enough to make the King snap.
あぁ…！
What we're doing is cruel.
生まれながらの能力者！ 軍団長殿は どの系統にも分類できない
We are no different from them. No...
特質系ということですな。
We are far worse!
ハッ！
Pitou... Pitou...